Guide to the Tamiment Library Newspapers PERIODICALS.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- G
  - The Government Standard Place of publication: Washington, D.C. Publisher: American Federation of Government Employees, AFL-CIO, 1984-1985 (Box 25)
  - La Grande guerre par les artistes Place of publication: Paris, France Publisher: Berger-Levrault et Georges Cres and Co., 1914 (Box 174)
  - Granma International Place of publication: Havana, Cuba, 2001-2002 (Box 173A)
  - Granma Weekly Review Place of publication: Havana, Cuba Publisher: Partido Comunista de Cuba, 1978 (Box 174)
  - Granpa Place of publication: New York, N.Y., 1967-1968 (Box 171)
  - Grape Place of publication: Vancouver, Canada, 1972-1973 (Box 471-472)
  - Grapes of Wrath Place of publication: Norfolk, Va. Publisher: The Defense Committee-Tidewater, 1972-1975 (Box 163)
  - The Grapevine Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: Concerned Truckers for a Democratic Union, 1975-1976 (Box 501)
  - Graphic Communicator Place of publication: Washington, D.C. Publisher: Graphic Communications Union, 1983-current (Box 172-173)
  - Grass Roots: La Voz del Harlem Este Place of publication: New York, N.Y., 1965 (Box 223)
  - Grass Roots: National Newsletter of the People's Party Place of publication: Washington, D.C. Publisher: People's Party, 1972-1975 (Box 174)
  - Grass Roots Forum Place of publication: San Gabriel, Calif. Publisher: Grass Roots Publishing Co., 1972-1980 (Box 175)
  - Grass Roots of Indianapolis Place of publication: Indianapolis, Ind. (Box 174)
  - Gray Panther Network: Age and Youth in Action Place of publication: Philadelphia, Pa. Publisher: Gray Panther Network, 1975-1987 (Box 176)
  - Great Speckled Bird Place of publication: Atlanta, Ga. Publisher: Atlanta Cooperative News Project, 1971-1974 (Box 176)
  - Green Action Place of publication: Tempe, Ariz. Publisher: Grassroots People's Coalition, 1987 (Box 176)
  - Green Politics Place of publication: Kansas City, Mo. Publisher: Greens/Green Party USA, 1992-1997 (Box 178)
  - Green Revolution, 1972-1981 (Box 123)
  - The Green Revolution Place of publication: Freeland, Md. Publisher: The School of Living, 1967-1981 (Box 123)
  - El grito del norte Place of publication: Espanola, N.M., 1968-1993 (Box 128)
  - Grito y fusil Place of publication: Quebec, Canada Publisher: Center for Information on Latin America, 1972 (Box 223)
  - Guardian Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Weekly Guardian Associates, 1968-1990 (Box 435)
    Researchers must use microfilm (Film R-7058)
  - Guerilla Place of publication: Toronto, Canada, nd (Box 248)
  - Guild Bulletin Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: New York Teachers Guild, 1956-1960 (Box 66)
  - Guild Bulletin / New York Teachers Guild Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: New York Teachers Guild, 1941-1947 (Box 65)
  - Guild Forum Place of publication: Washington, D.C. Publisher: Washington-Baltimore Newspaper Guild, Local 35 TNG, AFL-CIO, CLC, 1979 (Box 177A)
  - Guild Memo Place of publication: Detroit, Mich. Publisher: Newspaper Guild of Detroit-CIO, 1948 (Box 177A)
  - Guild Notes Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: National Lawyers Guild, 1972-1988 (Box 177)
  - Guild Progressive Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Independent Progressive Members of the Newspaper Guild of NYC, 1940 (Box 176)
  - Guild Reporter Place of publication: Washington, D.C. Publisher: Newspaper Guild and Communications Reporter, 1947-current (Box 176A-176B)
    Researchers must use microfilm (Film R-7066)
  - Guild Teacher Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: New York Teachers Guild, 1936-1942 (Box 65)
  - Guild Telegram and Sun Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: World-Telegram and Sun Unit of Newspaper Guild of New York, 1950 (Box 178)
  - Gulf Coast Fish Cheer Place of publication: Pensacola, Fla. Publisher: Pensacola Co-op News Service c/o Universal Life Church, 1971 (Box 178)
- H
  - Haiti progres Place of publication: Brooklyn, N.Y. Publisher: Haiti Progres, 2003 (Box 178)
  - The Hard Core Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Columbia Students for a Democratic Society, 1968-1969 (Box 178)
  - Hard Times Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: National Lawyers Guild, University of Chicago Chapter, 1975-1976 (Box 179)
  - Hard Times Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Hard Times Conference, 1976 (Box 178)
  - Harlem News Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Architects' Renewal Committee in Harlem, 1971-nd (Box 38)
  - Harrisburg Independent Press Place of publication: Harrsiburg, Pa. Publisher: Harrisburg Independent Press, Inc., 1972 (Box 179)
  - Harry Place of publication: Baltimore, Md. Publisher: Atlantis Pub. Co., 1970 (Box 178)
  - Hartford's Other Voice Place of publication: Hartford, Conn., 1969-1970 (Box 178)
  - Hawaii Free Peoples Press Place of publication: Haleiwa, Hawaii, 1970 (Box 178)
  - Health Liberation News Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Medical Committee for Human Rights, 1971-1973 (Box 183)
  - Health Rights News Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: Medical Committee for Human Rights, 1968-1972 (Box 178)
  - Healthwire Place of publication: Washington, D.C. Publisher: American Federation of Teachers, 1981 (Box 488)
  - 'Heights and 'Valley News Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Columbia Tenants Union, 1973-1978 (Box 178)
  - Hell on Wheels / By and For the Rank and File of TWU Local 100 Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Rank and File Movement in Local 100, 1984-2001 (Box 179)
  - The Helping Hand Place of publication: Mountain Home, Idaho, 1972-1973 (Box 163)
  - Henderson Station Place of publication: Pa. Publisher: Penn State College, 1971 (Box 178)
  - Hera Place of publication: Philadelphia, Pa. Publisher: Hera, Inc., 1975 (Box 477)
  - Herald Tribune Place of publication: Brooklyn, N.Y., nd (Box 178)
  - Heritage Place of publication: Los Angeles, Calif., 1957 (Box 180)
  - Her-self Place of publication: Ann Arbor, Mich. Publisher: Her-self, 1972-1975 (Box 178)
  - Hey Teach! Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Teachers for a Democratic Society, 1969-1969? (Box 281)
  - The High School Student Mobilizer Place of publication: U.S.A., nd (Box 281)
  - The Highlander Place of publication: Riverside, Calif. Publisher: UC-Riverside, 1971 (Box 477)
  - Hoe Hana Place of publication: Honolulu, Hawaii Publisher: Labor Community Alliance, 1974-1975 (Box 181)
  - Hollywood Free Paper Place of publication: Hollywood, Calif. Publisher: Jesus People International, nd (Box 183)
  - Homefront Place of publication: Dallas, Tex. (Box 181)
  - Hooka Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Humanitarian Order of Kosmic Awareness, 1970-1972 (Box 180)
  - Hospital Reporter Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Hospital and Medical Employees Union, Local 444, UPW, 1952 (Box 487)
  - Hospital Workers United Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Hospital Workers United, 1973-1974 (Box 180)
  - The Hot Seat / Taxi Rank and File Coalition Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Taxi Rank and File Coalition, 1971-1977 (Box 183)
  - Hotchpot Place of publication: Cleveland, Ohio, 1971 (Box 180)
  - Hotel Voice Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: New York Hotel and Motel Trades Council, AFL-CIO and Local 6, Hotel, Restaurant, Club Employees and Bartenders Union, AFL-CIO, 1983-current (Box 181-182B)
  - Hotel/Restaurant Voice Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: New York Hotel and Motel Trades Council, AFL-CIO and Local 6, Hotel, Restaurant, Club Employees and Bartenders Union, 1979-1983 (Box 181)
  - Housestaff Voice Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: National Federation of Housestaff Organizations, 1989-1992 (Box 191)
  - Houston Breakthrough Place of publication: Houston, Tex. Publisher: Breakthrough Publishing Co., 1976-1979 (Box 163)
  - L'Humanité nouvelle, 1968 (Box 183)
  - L'Humanité rouge Place of publication: Paris, France, 1969 (Box 183)
  - Hundred Flowers Place of publication: Minneapolis, Minn. Publisher: Hundred Flowers, 1970-1971 (Box 183)
  - Hunter Envoy: The Student Voice of Hunter College Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Hunter Envoy, 1998 (Box 111)
  - Huracán Place of publication: Minneapolis, Minn. Publisher: Alliance for Cultural Democracy, 1990-1990 (Box 183)
  - Hydro Focus: A Fortnightly People's Newspaper Produced by and for the Hydro Region Workers and Residents Publisher: Upper Mazaruni Development Project, 1976 (Box 183)
  - Hysteria Place of publication: U.S.A., nd (Box 281)
  - Hysteria Place of publication: Boston, Mass., 1970-1971 (Box 477)
- I
  - IBT News Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1947 (Box 184)
  - Iconoclast Place of publication: Surrey, England Publisher: Millar, J.A., 1971 (Box 184)
  - Ideas & Action Place of publication: San Francisco, Calif., 1982-1991 (Box 191)
  - L'Idiot International Place of publication: Paris, France, 1971 (Box 185)
  - L'Idiot Liberté Place of publication: Paris, France, 1971 (Box 185)
  - Illinois State Federation of Labor Weekly Newspaper Place of publication: Ill., 1920-1940 (Box 185)
  - In Public Service Place of publication: Washington, D.C. Publisher: Public Employee Department, 1979-1981 (Box 488)
  - In Struggle Place of publication: Canada Publisher: Canadian Proletarian Party, 1977 (Box 185)
  - In Public Service Place of publication: Washington, D.C. Publisher: AFL-CIO Public Employee Dept., 1975-1983 (Box 185)
  - In Public Service Place of publication: Washington, D.C. Publisher: Public Employee Department, 1979-1981 (Box 488)
  - In These Times Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: New Majority Pub. Co., 1976-1991 (Box 185A-188)
  - In Transit: Official Journal / Amalgamated Transit Union Place of publication: Washington, D.C. Publisher: Amalgamated Transit Union, 1967-1988 (Box 192-193)
  - The Incredible Bureaucrat Place of publication: New York, N.Y., 1969 (Box 189)
  - The Independent Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Expose Inc., 1955-1964 (Box 189, 194-195)
  - The Independent Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Independent Citizens Committee for the Arts, Sciences and Professions, 1945-1946 (Box 185)
  - Independent Peoples Tribunal Newsletter Place of publication: Oakland, Calif. Publisher: National Continuing Committee for an Independent Peoples Tribunal, 1970-nd (Box 248)
  - Independent Politics News: A Publication of the Independent Progressive Politics Network Place of publication: Brooklyn, N.Y. Publisher: Independent Progressive Politics Network, 1997-2003 (Box 189)
  - Independent Socialist Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: New York Independent Socialist Club, 1967-1969 (Box 189)
  - Indianapolis Free Press Place of publication: Indianapolis, Ind. Publisher: Radical Pub. Co. of Ind., Inc., 1970 (Box 189)
  - Individuo nella società Place of publication: Italy, 1979-1980 (Box 189)
  - Indochina Focal Point Place of publication: Santa Monica, Calif. Publisher: Indochina Peace Campaign, 1973-1975 (Box 189)
  - Industrial Worker Place of publication: Ypsilanti, Mich. Publisher: Industrial Workers of the World, 1994-current (Box 205A)
  - Indypendent: The Newspaper of NYC-IMC Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: New York City Independent Media Center, 2000-current (Box 190)
  - INFACT News Place of publication: Minneapolis, Minn. Publisher: INFACT, nd (Box 189)
  - Informations ouvrières Place of publication: Paris, France, 1968-1985 (Box 196-201)
  - Les Informations politiques et socials Place of publication: Paris, France Publisher: Pagos al Centre d'Archives et de Documentation Politiques et Sociales, 1965 (Box 28)
  - Infusion: Tools for Action and Education Place of publication: Cambridge, Mass. Publisher: Center for Campus Organizing, 1998-1999 (Box 111)
  - Iniziativa anarchica Place of publication: Pisa, Italy Publisher: Iniziativa Anarchica, 1965-1966 (Box 189)
  - Inner City Press Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Inner City Press, 1988-1994 (Box 191)
  - Inner City Voice Place of publication: Detroit, Mich. Publisher: League of Revolutionary Black Workers, 1967-1971 (Box 201)
  - Inside Out Place of publication: Ann Arbor, Mich. Publisher: Prisoner's Progress Association, 1975 (Box 341)
  - The Insurgent Place of publication: Eugene, Or. Publisher: The Insurgent, 2000-2001 (Box 201)
  - Insurrection Place of publication: Paterson, N.J., nd (Box 201)
  - Inter-com Place of publication: West Palm Beach, Fla. Publisher: Locals 3112-3111, Communications Workers of America (A.F.L.-C.I.O.), 1979 (Box 115C)
  - Inter-Hemispheric Education Resource Center Bulletin Place of publication: Albuquerque, N.M. Publisher: Inter-Hemispheric Education Resource Center, 1986 (Box 191)
  - International Chemical Worker Place of publication: Akron, Ohio Publisher: ICWU, 1970-1974 (Box 202)
  - International Fire Fighter Place of publication: Washington, D.C. Publisher: International Association of Fire Fighters, 1981-1986 (Box 202)
  - International Labor Defender Place of publication: New Haven, Conn. Publisher: International Committee for United Front International Labor Defense, 1982 (Box 202)
  - International Molders and Allied Workers Union Journal Place of publication: Washington, D.C. Publisher: International Molders and Allied Workers Union, 1972-1988 (Box 203)
  - International Musician: Official Journal of the American Federation of Musicians of the United States and Canada Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: American Federation of Musicians of the United States and Canada, 1997-current (Box 203A-203D)
  - International Operating Engineer Place of publication: Washington, D.C. Publisher: International Union of Operating Engineers, 1998-2005 (Box 85)
  - International Woodworker Place of publication: Portland, Or. Publisher: International Woodworkers of America, 1978-1987 (Box 204)
  - International Worker Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: International Worker's Party, 1974-1976 (Box 205)
  - International Workers Bulletin Place of publication: Oak Park, Ill. Publisher: Socialist Equality Party, 1994-1997 (Box 207A)
  - Internationale Place of publication: Paris, France Publisher: Alliance Marxiste Révolutionnaire, 1970 (Box 205)
  - International Workers Bulletin Place of publication: Southfield, Mich. Publisher: Workers League, 1994-1997 (Box 207)
  - Internationalism Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: International Communist Current in the U.S., 1991-current (Box 218)
  - Internationalist Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Mundial Publications, 1997-current (Box 218)
  - Internationalist Worker Place of publication: New Haven, Boston, New York Conn., Mass., N.Y. Publisher: Revolutionary Communist League, 1974-1979 (Box 205)
  - Intertribal News Service, 1971 (Box 403)
  - The Iowa City Oppressed Citizen Place of publication: Iowa City, Iowa, nd (Box 205)
  - Iowa Union Farmer Place of publication: Columbus Junction, Iowa Publisher: B.H. Shearer, 1954 (Box 184)
  - Irish Militant Place of publication: London, England, 1966-1968 (Box 435)
  - Irish Worker Place of publication: London, England, 1962 (Box 435)
  - Issue Place of publication: Columbia, Mo. Publisher: Ideographics INC., 1971-nd (Box 206)
  - Issues: St. Paul Dispatch Place of publication: U.S.A. Publisher: Pioneer Press, 1972 (Box 341)
  - It Ain't Me Babe Place of publication: Berkeley, Calif. Publisher: Women's Liberation, 1970-1971 (Box 206)
  - ITU Review Place of publication: Colorado Springs, Colo. Publisher: Executive Council of the International Typographical Union, 1964-1982 (Box 183)
  - IUE-CWA News Place of publication: Washington, D.C. Publisher: International Union of Electric, Electrical, Salaried, Machine and Furniture Workers - Communication Workers of America, 1996-2001 (Box 218)
  - IUPIW Views Place of publication: Paramount, Calif. Publisher: International Union of Petroleum & Industrial Workers, SIUNA, AFL-CIO, 1973-1984 (Box 184)
  - IUSY Survey Place of publication: Amsterdam, Netherlands Publisher: International Union of Socialist Youth, 1952-1968 (Box 184)
- J
  - J.P. Stevens Boycott News Place of publication: Boston, Mass. Publisher: Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union, 1977-1978 (Box 206)
  - Jailbreak: High School Youth Against War and Fascism Place of publication: New York, N.Y., 1970-1971 (Box 281)
  - Jane Doe Place of publication: Romulus, N.Y. Publisher: Women's Encampment for a Future of Peace and Justice, 1985 (Box 206)
  - JDL & Soviet Jewry Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Jewish Defense League, 1971 (Box 206)
  - Jericho Place of publication: Portland, Or. Publisher: Joint Committee, 1971?-1972 (Box 341)
  - Jericho Place of publication: Washington, D.C. Publisher: National Moratorium on Prison Construction, 1976-1984 (Box 341)
  - Jeugd / Algemeen Nederlands Jeugd Verbond Place of publication: Amsterdam, Netherlands Publisher: ANJV, 1971 (Box 206)
  - Jeune revolutionnaire Place of publication: Paris, France Publisher: Alliance des Jeunes pour le Socialisme, 1968-1972 (Box 208)
  - Jewish Liberation Journal Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Jewish Liberation Project, 1969-1972 (Box 208)
  - Jewish Museum Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Jewish Museum, 1987-1988 (Box 208)
  - The Jewish Radical Place of publication: Berkeley, Calif. Publisher: Union of Jewish Students, 1969-1972 (Box 208)
  - Jobs with Peace Campaign Report Place of publication: Boston, Mass. Publisher: National Jobs with Justice Campaign, 1992 (Box 208)
  - Jones Family's Grandchildren Place of publication: Norman, Okla. Publisher: SDS, 1968 (Box 208)
  - El Josco Place of publication: Boston, Mass. Publisher: Puerterrian Rebel Socialist Party, nd (Box 223)
  - Journal Place of publication: Washington, D.C. Publisher: International Union of Bricklayers and Allied Craftsmen, 1982-1988 (Box 208)
  - The Journal Place of publication: Rochester, N.Y., 1971 (Box 208)
  - Juche Place of publication: Cambridge, Mass. Publisher: People's Information Center Collective and White Panther Tribe, 1970-1971 (Box 208)
  - Jump Cut Place of publication: Berkeley, Calif. Publisher: Jump Cut Associates, 1974-1986 (Box 208A)
  - Justice: The Official Organ of the International Ladies Garment Workers Union Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, 1972-1995 (Box 209-212)
  - Justice Speaks Place of publication: Rocky Mount, Publisher: Black Workers for Justice, 1993-2005 (Box 218)
  - Juventud rebelde Place of publication: Havana, Cuba Publisher: Juventud Rebelde, 1978 (Box 218)
- K
  - Ka Huliau Place of publication: Honolulu, Hawaii Publisher: Hawaii Education for Social Progress, Inc., 1983-1986 (Box 213)
  - Kadima Place of publication: Champaign, Ill. Publisher: Jewish Student Association, 1971 (Box 213)
  - Kalayaan Place of publication: San Francisco, Calif., 1971-1972 (Box 31)
  - Kaleidoscope Place of publication: Milwaukee, Wis., 1970-1971 (Box 213)
  - Katipunan Place of publication: Oakland, Calif. Publisher: Katipunan Publications, 1988-1989 (Box 214)
  - Keep Left Place of publication: London, England Publisher: Young Socialists, 1961-1971 (Box 497)
  - Kent Dragonfire Place of publication: Kent, Ohio Publisher: Y.I.P., [1971] (Box 213)
  - Kick It Over Place of publication: Toronto, Canada Publisher: Kick It Over Collective, 1983-1990 (Box 213)
  - King Street Trolley Place of publication: Madison, Wis. Publisher: Liberation News Service, 1971 (Box 214)
  - Krokodil Place of publication: Moscow, U.S.S.R. Publisher: Izd. Gazety "Pravda", 1930-1959 (Box 213)
  - Kudzu Place of publication: Jackson, Miss., 1970-1972 (Box 214)
  - Kuguk Chonson: The National Salvation Front Place of publication: Tokyo, Japan Publisher: Mission of the National Democratic Front of South Korean in Japan, 1997-1999 (Box 214)
  - Kultur Place of publication: Chicago, Ill., 1925-1926 (Box 214A)
- L
  - L.A. Catalyst Place of publication: Los Angeles, Calif. Publisher: Catalyst Collective, nd (Box 213)
  - Lab-Log Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Motion Picture Laboratory Technicians, Local 702, IATSE, 1949 (Box 213)
  - Labor Place of publication: Washington, D.C. Publisher: Labor Cooperative Educational and Publishing Society, 1936-1984 (Box 214A)
  - Labor Action Publisher: Labor Action Committee, 1970-1973 (Box 435)
  - Labor Action Place of publication: San Francisco, Calif. Publisher: Labor Action Coalition, 2004 (Box 220)
  - Labor Chronicle Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: New York City Central Labor Council, 1965-1984 (Box 220)
  - Labor Defender Place of publication: Detroit, Mich. Publisher: Civil Rights Congress of Michigan, 1952-1954 (Box 220)
  - Labor Herald Place of publication: Baltimore, Md., 1942-1976 (Box 215-216)
  - Labor Militant Place of publication: Oakland, Calif. Publisher: Labor Militant Collective, 1986-1990 (Box 215)
  - Labor News Place of publication: Eureka, Calif. Publisher: Labor News, 1905 (Box 220)
  - Labor News Place of publication: Rochester, N.Y. Publisher: Central Trades and Labor Council, 2004-2007 (Box 216A)
  - Labor Page: A Publication of City Life Place of publication: Jamaica Plain, Mass. Publisher: Community News Publishers, 1986-1998 (Box 217)
  - Labor Party Press Place of publication: Washington, D.C. Publisher: Labor Party, 1996?-2002 (Box 220)
  - Labor Today Place of publication: Detroit, Mich. Publisher: Association for Economic Studies, 1971-1987 (Box 219A)
  - Labor Unity Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers, 1982-1995 (Box 221-222)
  - Labor Voice for Peace Publisher: Labor Leadership Assembly for Peace, 1968 (Box 215)
  - LaboReport on Central America Place of publication: Oakland, Calif. Publisher: Labor Network on Central America, 1985-1989 (Box 220)
  - Labor's Champion: Organ of the Central Committee of the Revolutionary Political Organization (Marxist-Leninist) USA Place of publication: New Orleans, La. Publisher: Revolutionary Political Organization, 1985-1991 (Box 217)
  - Labor's Voice Place of publication: Louisville, Ky. Publisher: Labor's Voice Publishing Company, 1950 (Box 487)
  - Labour Press Service Place of publication: London, England, 1941-1950 (Box 219A)
  - Lancaster Independent Press Place of publication: Lancaster, Publisher: Lancaster Independent Press, Inc., 1972-1984 (Box 219A)
  - Las Vegas Free Press Place of publication: Las Vegas, Nev., 1970 (Box 219A)
  - The Lather Place of publication: Washington, D.C. Publisher: The Wood, Wire and Metal Lathers International Union, 1977-1979 (Box 487)
  - Latino Place of publication: New York, N.Y., 1970 (Box 223)
  - Lavender Vision Place of publication: Cambridge, Mass. Publisher: Media Collective (Box 165)
  - Lavender Woman Place of publication: Chicago, Ill., 1971 (Box 477)
  - The Leader Place of publication: Ottawa, Canada Publisher: Canadian Union of Public Employees, 1986-1996 (Box 220)
  - Leadership News Place of publication: Arlington, Va. Publisher: American Association of School Administrators, 1991 (Box 487)
  - Legislative Conference News / Published by the Legislative Conference of the City University of New York Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Legislative Conference of CUNY, 1964-1968 (Box 219)
  - The Legislative Gazette Place of publication: Albany, N.Y. Publisher: State University of New York College at New Paltz, 1993 (Box 219A)
  - Lesbians Rising Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Hunter College, 1981 (Box 219A)